would like to mention I have Sarah baly
uh I'd like to get that out of the way
early in the show
uh I do talk about it a little bit you
know there's a few reasons I talk about
it number one is I've come to find if I
don't mention
it after a little
while the audience is
like does he know
[Laughter]
that he has
that another big reason is everything I
talk about comes from the perspective of
a disabled person right I mean this is
all that I've ever
known I guess I'll admit that early in
my career I try to do my show from a
Southern bell point of view
could never get that to play quite right
you
know dear
diary haven't been right since Mr Earl
left you guys are a fun crowd man
was although I could uh definitely say
there's a few people still looking at me
like what's after this a juggler
come on
yeah Fernando and you're going to love
him yeah he can juggle other
[Music]
midgets so if you are one you
know just be
ready the bar might not be as dryer
after
this well you looking at me that that
guy does not look dry at all I'm telling
you it's clean comedy you should take a
shower
first thank you I do I took two showers
today I just look dirty I don't know
what it is
know people always ask me if this
bracelet is one of those copper magnetic
healing
bracelets I like oh does that thing
work oh yeah man I was in a wheelchair
last
week this thing's been kicking some butt
for me
man I'm going to put it on this arm next
[Applause]
week actually I better take it off soon
you know I don't want to get too
better I might mess up my gig you know